rally.io 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy | Rally

Last Updated: 7/3/2012 

Irecess knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy is a binding part of Irecess's Website Terms of Use and End User License Agreement ("Agreement") and explains the type of information Irecess collects through its website and browser companion software ("Toolbar Service") and what Irecess does with it. If you download and use Irecess's Toolbar Service software or use the Irecess website, you will be bound by the terms of the Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently. 

Irecess is a Web Information Company. We measure Internet activity in order to understand trends, help people discover new content, and help people make better online decisions. Millions of people download Irecess toolbars (browser extensions) to help measure the web. In return, Irecess may provide toolbar users with information about Internet trends, website popularity, new and exciting topics, and other interesting content. 

NOTE: IRECESS'S TOOLBAR SERVICE COLLECTS AND STORES INFORMATION ABOUT THE WEB PAGES YOU VIEW. IN SOME CASES, INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE TOOLBAR SERVICE MAY BE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, BUT PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT AT Irecess, AND WE DO NOT ATTEMPT TO ANALYZE WEB USAGE DATA TO DETERMINE THE IDENTITY OF ANY Irecess USER. 

## What Personal Information About Users Does Irecess Gather?

The information we learn from users helps us continually improve and provide information about Internet trends, website popularity, new and exciting topics, and related content. Here are the types of information we gather. 

Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way, including personal information about other people that you provide to us. Scroll down, to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing and improving our services, and communicating with you. 

Automatic Information We Collect From the Toolbar Service: When you use the Toolbar Service, we collect information about the websites you visit and the advertisements that you see on those websites, the searches you perform using search engines and when you use the "search" function of the Toolbar Service, the ways in which you use various Toolbar Service features (including whether the Toolbar Service is still installed on your computer), and the pages you view. [Click here] to see examples of what we collect. Although this information may contain some personally identifiable information, Irecess does not use it to determine the identity of individual users or correlate it to your email address or other personally identifiable information that you give us or our affiliates, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, or other legal requirements. 

Automatic Information We Collect from Our Website: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Irecess.com, when you use the Toolbar Service, or when you view advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Irecess.com on other Web sites. 

Automatic Information We Collect from Other Websites: We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with third-party websites that you have logged in to through our authentication. 

Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources. 

## What About Cookies and Web Beacons?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser, and through our Toolbar Service, to enable our systems to recognize your browser. When you visit our Websites or use our offerings, whether or not you are a registered member, we may send one or more cookies to your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on a website. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits. Persistent cookies can be removed. However, without cookies you will not have access to certain services on the Mavn.me Site. Third party advertisements displayed in connection with our websites and apps may also contain cookies set by internet advertisers. We do not control these cookies and users should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. We may also use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our websites. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. 

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

## Does Irecess Share the Information it Receives?

We share Irecess user data with the subsidiaries it controls, and we may share personally identifying information with third parties only as described below. 

Businesses We Do Not Control: We may offer search or other services that are powered or provided by another company. You can tell when a third party is involved in a given service offering, and, if you choose to use the service, we will share information related to your use of the service with that company. For example, if you use a third-party search engine offered through our Toolbar Service, we will transmit your search term and IP address to that company so that it can provide you with the requested search results. Likewise, if you download our Toolbar Service from a third party website, the Toolbar Service may display the third party's brand, and consequently that third party may receive information about your use of the Toolbar Service. 

Third-Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include storing and analyzing data, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), providing customer service, and payment processing. They have access to user information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the event that Irecess or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

Protection of Irecess and Others: We release account and other user information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Irecess, our users, or others. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from users for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when personally identifiable information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

## How Secure Is Information About Me?

Irecess uses commercially reasonable computer security safeguards to protect its databases and servers against risks of loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, or inadvertent or improper disclosure of data. 

Irecess segregates certain personally identifiable and other information about your use of Irecess's services into separate databases, some of which can be accessed only by a limited number of employees. 

If you have an Irecess account, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

## What About Third-Party Advertising and Links to Other Websites?

We work with third-party websites, advertisers, and Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, (collectively, "Ad Companies"). These Ad Companies may send (or "serve") advertisements directly to your browser, from our website, our Toolbar Service, and from other websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. The information practices of these Ad Companies are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

## Which Information Can I Access?

If you create an Irecess account, we give you access to the personally identifiable information that you provide to us. [Click here] to see your account information or edit your profile. 

## What Choices Do I Have?

Irecess does not require that you provide us with personally identifiable information in order to use most of Irecess's services. Therefore, you can always choose not to provide such information. 

You may disable the Toolbar Service from reporting information about your web surfing activities and/or statistics about your use of the Toolbar Service by using the Options menu in the Toolbar Service. 

You may disable the Toolbar Service from sending Irecess any web page, advertisement, or search term information by uninstalling the software. 

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

The Toolbar Service enables you to update certain browser configuration settings, such as your home page or your default search provider. If supported, you may configure these options during the installation process and in the Options menu in the Toolbar Service. 

## Are Children Allowed to Use Irecess?

Irecess does not offer products or services for use by children. If you are under 18, you may use Irecess's website or the Toolbar Service only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Irecess or use the Toolbar Service, any dispute with Irecess over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at Irecess, please contact with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Website Terms of Use will change also. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

## Examples of Information Collected

### Information You Give Us

You provide most such information when you use our website or the Toolbar Service. For instance, if you register for an account at Irecess, we collect your name, email address, country of origin, and, if you choose, your nickname, telephone number, website, company, and title. If you download and install the Toolbar Service software, which provides the Irecess toolbar, we collect any information voluntarily provided by you during the installation and registration process, which can include demographic information such as gender, age, occupation, household income, zip code and country. Demographic information is correlated to Web usage information collected during your use of the Toolbar Service. In addition, you might provide us with personally identifiable information when you communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise or complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form. 

### Automatic Information We Collect From the Toolbar Service

When you download the Toolbar Service, and at times during your use of the Irecess website and Toolbar Service, we transmit Irecess cookies to the hard drive of your computer. In addition, for every Web page you view while using the Toolbar Service, the Irecess software transmits and stores your IP address, which may include a domain name, the full URL of the Web page you are visiting, general information about your browser; general information about your computer's operating system; your Irecess cookie number or other identifying alphanumerical information enabling Irecess to identify your computer; and the date and time the above information is logged. All of this above information is logged together in a single data string for each Web page you visit. Each string is logged in our database in the chronological order received from our millions of users. The Toolbar Service also automatically collects information about the online advertisements that are displayed on the websites you visit - specifically, the text, source, and URL of the online ad - and the terms you choose when you use search engines to search the Web. You may disable the Toolbar Service from sending Irecess any web page, advertisement, or search term information by turning off all Web Information features listed in the Options menu in the Toolbar Service. 

Irecess also periodically collects usage statistics from Toolbar Service users that describe the frequency of use of each Toolbar Service feature. You may disable the Toolbar Service from sending Irecess usage statistics information at any time by using the Options menu in the Toolbar Service. 

Finally, to ensure accurate information about the number of Toolbar Service users, the Toolbar Service periodically sends a signal to Irecess containing basic information such as the IP address of your computer. 

### Automatic Information We Collect From Our Website

Examples of the information we collect and analyze when you use our website include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie; web pages you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call us. During some visits to our website we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

### Automatic Information We Collect From Other Websites

Examples of automatic information we collect from third-party websites include the account identifier for the website, the URL’s of web pages visited, any referring URL’s to the visited web pages, the IP addresses and browser user-agents of visitors, and a unique identifier for each visitor. 

### Information from Other Sources

An example of information we might receive from other sources is when you authorize a third party website , such as Facebook, to interact directly with the Toolbar Service or our website to provide or receive personalized information about you. In that case, we might receive such information as your name and potentially other information used by that third party website to identify your account with that website.
